let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "People speak Portuguese in Brazil.",
    answer: "Portuguese is spoken in Brazil.",
    options: [
      "Portuguese is spoken in Brazil.",
      "Portuguese was spoken in Brazil.",
      "Portuguese has spoken in Brazil.",
      "Portuguese were spoken in Brazil."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The Government is planning a new road near my house.",
    answer: "A new road is being planned near my house.",
    options: [
      "A new road was being planned near my house.",
      "A new road were being planned near my house.",
      "A new road is being planned near my house.",
      "A new road will have being planned near my house."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "My grandfather built this house in 1943.",
    answer: "This house was built by my grandfather in 1943.",
    options: [
      "This house is built by my grandfather in 1943.",
      "This house was built by my grandfather in 1943.",
      "This house were built by my grandfather in 1943.",
      "This house will have built by my grandfather in 1943."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Picasso was painting Guernica at that time.",
    answer: "Guernica was being painted by Picasso at that time.",
    options: [
      "Guernica was being painted by Picasso at that time.",
      "Guernica were being painted by Picasso at that time.",
      "Guernica is being painted by Picasso at that time.",
      "Guernica are being painted by Picasso at that time."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The cleaner has cleaned the office.",
    answer: "The office has been cleaned.",
    options: [
      "The office have been cleaned.",
      "The office had been cleaned.",
      "The office will has been cleaned.",
      "The office has been cleaned."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "He had written three books before 1867.",
    answer: "Three books had been written before 1867.",
    options: [
      "Three books has been written before 1867.",
      "Three books have been written before 1867.",
      "Three books had been written before 1867.",
      "Three books will have been written before 1867."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "John will tell you later.",
    answer: "You will be told by John later.",
    options: [
      "You will told by John later.",
      "You will be told by John later.",
      "You would be told by John later.",
      "You will been told by John later."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "By this time tomorrow we will have signed the deal.",
    answer: "By this time tomorrow the deal will have been signed.",
    options: [
      "By this time tomorrow the deal will has been signed.",
      "By this time tomorrow the deal will be signed.",
      "By this time tomorrow the deal will have been signed.",
      "By this time tomorrow the deal will have being signed."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Somebody should do the work.",
    answer: "The work should be done.",
    options: [
      "The work should done.",
      "The work could be done.",
      "The works should be do.",
      "The work should be done."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The traffic might have delayed Jimmy.",
    answer: "Jimmy might have been delayed by the traffic.",
    options: [
      "Jimmy might has been delayed by the traffic.",
      "Jimmy might will have been delayed by the traffic.",
      "Jimmy might have been delayed by the traffic.",
      "Jimmy might will has been delayed by the traffic."
    ]
  },
];